#### Contact

(21)979381580 (Mobile) pablodiegoo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pablodiegoo (LinkedIn)

linktr.ee/pablo (Personal)

## Top Skills

Analytical Skills
Personal Financial Planning
Investments

## Languages

Português (Native or Bilingual) Inglês (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

EF SET English Certificate 79/100 (C2 Proficient)

Crowdfunding

Bitcoin and Cryptocurrency Technologies

Ask Questions to Make Data-Driven Decisions

**Specialist Advisory** 

# Pablo Diego Pereira

Partner at Meta Investimentos | Investments | Economics | Data Science and Analytics

Rio de Janeiro, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil

## Summary

Partner at Meta Investimentos, acting as an investment advisor and responsible for the area of controls and processes in RJ.

Alumni UFRJ (Institute of Economics), Mackenzie-Rio (extension in coaching) and USP (MBA in Data Science and Analytics). I have some of the main certifications in the Brazilian financial market: PQO (BM&FBovespa), Specialist Advisory (Proseek), AAI (Ancord), FBB100 (FEBRABAN)

My areas of interest are: economics, investments, financial planning, technology, business, cryptocurrencies and blockchain.

## Experience

XP INVESTIMENTOS
Registered Investment Advisor
May 2018 - Present (5 years 6 months)
Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

Meta Investimentos CoFounder Investment Advisor June 2020 - Present (3 years 5 months) Rio de Janeiro, Rio de Janeiro, Brasil

Meta&Actio

2 years 10 months

Investment Advisor August 2017 - May 2020 (2 years 10 months)

Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

Back Office Manager Partner May 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 4 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

### Back Office Employee August 2017 - May 2018 (10 months)

Espaço Champs Elysees 4 years 11 months

Advice Partner
July 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 5 months)

Principal Managing Partner January 2014 - July 2017 (3 years 7 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

#### **BX** House

Independent Marketing Consultant November 2002 - January 2014 (11 years 3 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

# Ayra Consultoria 8 months

Marketing and Communications Consultant April 2012 - August 2012 (5 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

Marketing and Communications Intern January 2012 - April 2012 (4 months)

Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

#### **AIESEC**

Marketing and Communications Associate May 2010 - February 2012 (1 year 10 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

UFRJ - Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro Intern Research Assistant June 2011 - January 2012 (8 months) Rio de Janeiro e Região, Brasil

## Education

UFRJ - Universidade Federal do Rio de Janeiro Bachelor's degree, Economics · (2010 - 2014)

# MBA USP/Esalq

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Data Science and Analytics  $\cdot$  (April 2023 - December 2024)